Guide to the Tennesse Williams Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries I.1: Cataloged Correspondence, 1920-1982
    - Williams, Tennessee To Herbert Machiz, Tangiers, Morocco, [ca. July 1962], (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Herbert Machiz, [Tangiers, Morocco], [ca. July 1962], (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Herbert Machiz, Barcelona, 15 Aug 1962, (1 telegram) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Herbert Machiz, [New York?], [31 Oct 1962], (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Herbert Machiz, [New York?], [Dec? 1962], (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Herbert Machiz, New York, 16 Jan 1963, (1 telegram) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Claire Luce, Key West, FL, 28 Feb 1963, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Sociedad General de Autores de la Argentina, [New York], 4 April 1963, (1 p. t.l.) (Box B)
      [copy]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Herbert Machiz, Key West, FL, 7 April 1963, (1 telegram) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edward Albee, London, 22 June 1963, (3 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Frederick Nicklaus, [New York], 14 Aug 1963, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [With a.n. on the same page; With envelope]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Frederick Nicklaus, [Johnson City, VA], [22 Aug 1963], (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Claire Luce, Abingdon, VA, 16 Sept 1963, (1 p. a.n.s.) (Box B)
      [sent With flowers on opening night of The Milk Train at the Barter Theatre in Abingdon]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bigelow, [New York], [1964?], (1 p. a.l.) (Box B)
      [With envelope With a.n. by Bigelow]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Herbert Machiz, [Key West, FL], [1964?], (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [signed "10" and With copy of related letter]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Frederick Nicklaus, [Key West, FL], [ca. 20 Jan 1964], (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Frederick Nicklaus, [New Orleans], 15 April 1964, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Frederick Nicklaus, New York, 4 Sept 1964, (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Josephine Healy, [New York], [17 Feb 1965], (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, New York, 22 Aug 1965, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, New York, 30 April 1966, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, New Orleans, 1 Nov 1966, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Josephine Healy, New Orleans, 7 Jan 1967, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, New York, 22 Jan 1967, (1 p t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, New York, 4 Feb 1967, (1 p t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Dakin Williams, New York, 23 Feb 1967, (1 telegram ) (Box B)
      [a.n. on bottom and back by Dakin [?]; removed from TW's copy of Paradise Lost]
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, New York, 17 April 1967, (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, [New York], 17 Sept 1967, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, St. Louis, MO, 7 Nov 1967, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, [New York], 21 Feb 1968, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, [Hollywood, CA], 14 Sept 1968, (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, Key West, FL, 25 April 1970, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Harold Hart, Key West, FL, 13 May 1970, (2 p. t.l.s. & a.l.s.) (Box B)
      [TW replied to Hart on letter Hart wrote TW; copy]
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, Key West, FL, 25 May 1970, (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, Key West, FL, 11 Aug 1970, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Frank Roberts, Key West, FL, 25 Aug 1970, (1 telegram) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Whom It May Concern, [Key West, FL], 26 Aug 1970, (1 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)
      [Authorizing Frank Roberts' television special]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Frank Roberts, [Miami, FL], 28 Aug 1970, (1 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Tom Buckley, Singapore, 31 October 1970, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [carbon]
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, Bangkok, 15 Nov 1970, (4 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To David Lobdell, On board the S.S. President Wilson, 12 Dec 1970, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Cheryl Crawford and Paul Bigelow, [Key West, FL], 29 May 1971, (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Tom Seligson, Key West, FL, 6 Jan 1972, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [With a.n. at bottom; With envelope]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Frank Roberts, New York, 2 March 1972, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Frank Roberts, New York, 5 March 1972, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To David McCain, n.p., 25 Jan. 1978, (1 p. t.l.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee Receipts of Mailgrams, v.p., 17 June 1976 - 12 July 1982, (9 p. 9 mailgrams) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Paul Bowles, n.p., 14 July 1978, (1 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Eleven (i.e. Gary Carter), n.p., ca. Oct 1979, (2 a.n.s.) (Box B)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Mrs. Bixler, n.p., 28 Aug 1980, (2 p. t.l. & a.l.) (Box B)
      [excerpts of two letters in re: TW's family]
    - Williams, Tennessee To the University of Texas, Humanities Department, New York, 27 Aug. 1981 & 25 Jan. 1983, (2 p. a.l.s. & t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [both photocopies]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Milton, n.p., 1981 - 1982, (15 p. 4 t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [includes related letters from Rex Goff and Mitch Douglas; all copies]
    - Williams, Tennessee Invitations to party at home of Ernest Hemingway, Key West, FL, 7 April 1982, (2 invitations) (Box B)
      [includes envelope]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Cheryl Crawford, Key West, FL, 1 Sept. 1982, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Windham, Donald To Josephine Healy, Venice, 7 June 1948, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box B)
    - Windham, Donald To New York Times Editors, New York, 19 Nov 1977, (2 p. t.l.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Paul Bigelow, New York, 4 July 1942, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Paul Bigelow, New York, 4 Sept 1942, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Paul Bigelow, Boston, [12 Sept 1945], (3 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, New York, 7 Jan. 1947 - 29 July 1948, (5 p. 3 t.l., 1 t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Paul Bigelow, New York, 19 June 1947, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Paul Bigelow, New York, 3 Feb 1948, (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Paul Bigelow, New York, 30 Mar 1948, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Paul Bigelow, New York, 21 June 1948, (1 telegram) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Paul Bigelow, New York, 30 June 1948, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Paul Bigelow, London, 18 July 1948, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Paul Bigelow, Paris, 23 July 1948, (1 a.p.c.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Paul Bigelow, New York, 3 Sept 1948, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Paul Bigelow, New York, 12 Oct 1948, (1 telegram) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey and William Liebling To Paul Bigelow, Chicago, 29 Dec 1950, (1 telegram) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Paul Bigelow, Westport, CN, [11 July 1951], (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Paul Bigelow, New York, 19 July 1951, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [With copy of letter encl.; With envelope]
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, New York, 21 May 1959 - 26 Oct 1960, (5 p. 2 t.l.s., 1 telegram, 2 t.l.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, n.p., 19[60?], (4 p. telegram) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Cheryl Crawford, New York, 15 Aug. 1960, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, New York, 12 Jan. 1961 - 17 July 1961, (5 p. 3 t.l.s., 1 t.n., 1 telegram) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, New York, 17 July 1961 - 25 Oct 1961, (7 p. 3 t.l.s., 1 t.n., 1 t.n.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, New York, 31 Jan. 1962 - 14 Dec 1962, (4 p. 4 t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [one carbon]
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, New York, 23 Jan. 1962 - 26 Feb. 1963, (5 p. 2 t.l., 1 t.l.s., 1 telegram, 1 t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [note: 1 letter written by Morton Leavy to Audrey Wood]
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, New York, 12 Feb. 1963, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, New York, 1 April 1963 - 9 May 1963, (5 p. 5 t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [2 have a.n. on bottom]
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, New York, 14 May 1963 - 29 Jan 1964, (7 p. 5 t.l.s., 1 a.n.s.) (Box B)
      [includes attached note written by Arthur Miller in re: probibiting his productions in South Africa; also includes envelope]
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, [New York], 11 June 1963, (2 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [With postcript note in hand of Audrey Wood]
    - Wood, Audrey To Lady Maria St. Just, New York, 6 Aug 1963, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, Westport, CN, 2? Jan 1963, (1 telegram) (Box B)
    - Wood, Audrey To Charles Bowden, n.p., 15 Aug 1963, (1 p. t.l.) (Box B)
      [carbon copy of letter dictated by Audrey Wood]
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, New York, 22 Jan. 1965 - 5 Dec. 1966, (5 p. 3 t.l.s., 1 t.n., 1 t.n.s. ) (Box B)
      [includes one envelope]
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, New York, 9 Dec. 1966 - 18 May 1970, (5 p. 3 t.l.s., 2 t.n.s.) (Box B)
      [includes letters by John Reich and Robert De Maria to Audrey Wood forwarded to TW]
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, New York, March 1967, (6 p. 5 t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [includes letters by others in re: Milktrain]
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, New York, 11 Nov. 1970 - 18 Dec. 1970, (6 p. 2 t.l.s.) (Box B)
      [one letter is missing the first page]
    - Wood, Audrey To Tennessee Williams, New York, 197[?] - 14 Jan. 1971, (6 p. 1 a.l.s., 1 t.l.s., 1 telegram) (Box B)
  - Subseries I.2: Daken Williams Files
    1907-1959. In Box 1 of General Correspondence. A collection of correspondence to and from Williams and family purchased by Columbia Rare Book and Manuscript Library through an auction house. There are several letters from Williams' parents, from his Dakin grandparents, and a few from or about his sister Rose. The letters shed light on Williams early years including his MGM period and his trip to Mexico.
    - Dakin, Rev. Walter To Dakin and Edwina Williams, v.p., n.d., February 11, 1947 to April 20, 1947, (7 p. 3 a. l.s., 1 card.) (Box 1, Folder 1)
      [Includes 3 envelopes; also includes 2 attached notes by DW]
    - Dakin, Walter E. to Tennessee Williams, n.p., March 29, ?, (4 p. 1 a.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Williams, Thomas Lanier To Edwina Williams, Knoxville, TN, 15 Aug. 1907, (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 2)
      [includes note from DW and envelope]
    - Isabel To Williams family, n.p., n.d., (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 2)
      [includes DW's attached note]
    - Williams, Rose and Walter E. Dakin To Edwina Williams, n.p., 24 Jan. 1922, (4 p. a.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 2)
      [includes note from DW]
    - Williams, Edwina To TW, parents, and family, v.p., 10 April 1937- April 12, 1937, n.d., (19 p. 3 a.l.s., 1 a.l., 1 p.c.s.) (Box 1, Folder 2)
      [includes two notes from DW]
    - Williams, Edwina To Rev. Walter Dakin, v.p., 26 June 1948 - 27 July 1948, (8 p. 3 a.ls., 2 p.c.s.) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Hays, Helen To Edwina Williams, New York, 15 Oct 1949, (1 t.n.) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, v.p., 17 Aug 1942 - 18 Nov 1950, (6 p. 1 t.l.s., 2 a.l.s., 2 telegram) (Box 1, Folder 3)
      [includes 2 envelopes]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams and Walter Dakin, v.p., 16 Dec. 1950 - 22 May 1951, (6 p. 2 t.l.s., 4 telegrams) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, v.p., 24 Sept. 1956 - 25 July 1959, (2 p. 2 t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 3)
      [includes 1 envelope]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, v.p., [193?]?, (7 p. 1 a.l.s., 2 t.l.s., 1 t.l.) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, v.p., n.d., (9 p. 5 t.l.s., 1 a.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 3)
      [1 t.l.s. is a photocopy]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, v.p., n.d., (4 p. 1 a.l.s., 1 t.l.s., 2 envelopes) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Family, v.p., 21 Sept. 1940 - 18 June 1943, (9 p. 4 t.l.s., 1 t.l.) (Box 1, Folder 4)
      [includes 3 envelopes; 1 t.l.s. With a.n. on bottom]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Family, v.p., 3 Dec. 1943 - n.d., (12 p. 3 t.l.s., 2 a.l.s., 1 t.l.) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Cornelius Williams, v.p., 28 Feb 1941 - n.d., (8 p. 2 a.l.s., 2 t.l.s., 1 t.l., 1 telegram) (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Dakin Williams, v.p., 1948 - n.d., (9 p. 2 t.l.s., 2 telegrams, 1 p.c.s., 1 a.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 6)
      [two letters are copies]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Rev. Walter Dakin, v.p., 14 Sept. 1931 - 27 Oct 1948, (17 p. 1 a.l.s., 4 t.l.s., 2 t.l.) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Rev. Walter Dakin, v.p., June 19, 1950 - May 3, 1953, (4 p. 3 t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Rev. Walter Dakin, v.p., n.d., (15 p. 4 t.l.s., 2 a.l.s., 2 t.l.) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Tennessee To St. Louis Medical Credit Bureau, n.p., 19 July 1938, (1 p. 1 t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Rose Williams, Columbia, MO, n.d., (2 p. 1 t.l.) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, v.p., 14 Jan. 1939 - n.d., (4 p.c.s., 1 t.n.s.) (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Williams, Tennessee To Edwina Williams, Rev. Walter Dakin and family, v.p., 19 Sept 1940 - n.d., (6 p.c.s.) (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Williams, Tennessee Postcard of TW in Mexico; auto registration material, [n.p.], [n.d.], (1 a.p.c.) (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Webb, Samuel To C.C. Williams, St. Louis, MO, 15 Mar. 1939, (2 p. a.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 9)
      [With note from DW, envelope]
    - Williams, Tennessee To Sandy, n.p., 21 Feb. 1944, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Dramatists Guild To Tennessee Williams, New York, 5 June 1939, (1 p. t.l.s.) (Box 1, Folder 9)
      [includes a.n.s. from TW at bottom]
    - Williams, Tennessee Clippings and Announcements, [n.p.], ca. 1940, (1 folder) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Subseries I.3: Letters Ffrom Agents & Publishers
    Collection of letters from Williams succession of agents--Audrey Wood, Bill Barnes, Mitch Douglas and ICM--and his publishers. The letters are in chronological order.
    - , [n.p.], 1940-1982, (4 folders) (Box 1, Folder 10-13)
    - MacGregor, Robert, New Directions, 1957-1981, () (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Doubleday and others Correspondence, [n.p.], 1956-1982, (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
  - Subseries I.4: General Correspondence, 1951-1983
    Correspondents include Hermione Baddeley, Keith Baxter, Paul Bigelow. Robert Carroll, Walter E. Dakin, Henry Faulkner, Margaret Leighton, Anne Meacham, Frank Merlo, Jose Quintero, Jane Smith, Vassilis Vogilis, Edwina and Dakin Williams. Fan mail is also included.
    - Last names A-C, [n.p.], [v.d.], (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 17-19)
    - Last Names: Carroll-H, [n.p.], [v.d.], (16 folders) (Box 2, Folder 1-16)
    - Last Names: Healy-Perrier, [n.p.], [v.d.], (31 folders) (Box 3, Folder 1-31)
    - Last Names: Persson-Z, [n.p.], [v.d.], (29 folders) (Box 4, Folder 1-29)
    - First Names: A-J, [n.p.], [v.d.], (1 folder) (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - First Names: K-W, [n.p.], [v.d.], (1 folder) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified, unsigned, empty envelopes, [n.p.], [v.d.], (3 folders) (Box 5, Folder 2-4)
    - Fan Mail, [n.p.], 1965-1982, (4 folders) (Box 5, Folder 5-8)
    - Fan Mail, [n.p.], 1965-1982, (6 folders) (Box 6, Folder 1-6)
- Series II: Works, 1945-1982 11 linear ft.
  The Works series is divided into the subseries: Plays and screenplays; Stories and poetry; Other works and related material; Works based on the writings of Tennessee Williams; Biography; Awards, Honors and Celebrations; and Works about Tennessee Williams. The files contain annotated manuscripts, draft pages, scripts, proofs, notes, flyers, programs, certificates and clippings, dating primarily from the 1960s and 1970s.
  - Subseries II.1: Plays and Screenplays, 1937-1982
    This subseries contains script pages, scripts, notes, programs, clippings, reviews and essays. It is arranged alphabetically by title. See also production photographs in the Photography series.
    - Aimez-Vous Ionesco, [n.p.], [n.d.], (Draft pages, annotated) (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Baby Doll, [v.p.], 1956-1957, 1972, (Notes, clippings, pressbook, Academy Award nomination) (Box 7, Folder 2)
      [See also Tiger Tail and Twenty Seven Wagons Full of Cotton]
    - Balcony in Ferrara, [n.p.], [1937-1943?], (139 pp. t. ms. [Acq. 487-1986]) (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Battle of Angels, New York, Boston, 1940, (2 t. ms. used in Theater Guild production in Boston: Doris Dudley script [acq. 293-5.2.85]; script inscribed by Williams to Josephine Healy [acq. Friends 55052E]) (Box 7, Folder 4)
      [On microfilm. Master negative number 92-2107-3 and 92-2107-4. See also Orpheus Descending and The Fugitive Kind]
    - Battle of Angels, [n.p.], [n.d.] & 1974, (Draft pages, notes, clipping) (Box 7, Folder 5)
      [See also Orpheus Descending and The Fugitive Kind]
    - Blond Mediterraneans, [n.p.], [n.d.], (Draft pages) (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Boom, [n.p.], [n.d.], (Script pages, notes) (Box 7, Folder 7)
      [See also The Milk Train Doesn't Stop Here Anymore]
    - Camino Real, New York, [n.d.] & ca.1953, (Annotated draft pages [acq. 487/490-7188]; First draft of final version [BMC6-85003;9/12/85]; Appeal of support by artists, mimeograph [acq. Friends 55052E]; mimeographed script, Sixteen Blocks on the Camino Real [244526]; 2 1953 programs) (Box 7, Folder 8)
      [Also known as Sixteen Blocks on the Camino Real]
    - Camino Real, [n.p.], 1952-1977, (Script pages, notes, programs, clippings, reviews, letters, essays) (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
    - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, New York, 1954-1955, (t. script, December 9, 1954, 3 programs, clippings, photoprint of 1955 Drama Critics Award [BMC 702813], pressbook [acq. 278108]) (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, [n.p.], 1956-1982, (Script pages, programs, posters, clippings, reviews, essays, French version by Rene Dionne for 1982 Montreal production) (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - Clothes for a Summer Hotel, [n.p.], 1979-1980, ( Photocopied script, 1980. Photocopy of published script. Copy of "Zelda, A Millionaire's Girl" from Saturday Evening Post, May 7, 1930. Annotated script pages, article, music sheets, clippings, letters, program) (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
    - Confessional, [n.p.], [n.d.], (1 mimeographed script, Sidney Lanier copy, 1 of 100 signed by Williams) (Box 8, Folder 5)
      [See also Small Craft Warnings and Dragon Country]
    - Constructing Mobiles, [n.p.], [n.d.], (Annotated script pages) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Creve Coeur, New York, 1977-1978, (Annotated mimeographed script, October 1977. Annotated script pages, clippings, magazine) (Box 8, Folder 7)
      [See also A Lovely Sunday for Creve Coeur]
    - Dame Picque, [n.d.], (Typed script pages) (Box 8, Folder 8)
      [On microfilm. Master negative number 2000-2030]
    - Demolition Downtown, 1971, (letter, proofs) (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Eccentricities of a Nightingale, New York, 1978-1979, (Mimeographed script #20, 2 proofs, clippings, program) (Box 8, Folder 10)
      [See also Summer and Smoke]
    - Everlasting Ticket, [n.p.], [n.d.], (Annotated typed script pages) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - The Frosted Glass Coffin, New York, [n.d.], (Mimeographed script) (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Fugitive Kind, California, 1959, (Cutting and Dialog Continuities [acq: 269462]. Pressbooks [acq. 278110 and 491, 9/14/88]) (Box 9, Folder 3)
      [See also Battle of Angels and Orpheus Descending]
    - Gideon's Point, [n.p.], [n.d.], (Annotated draft t. ms. ) (Box 9, Folder 4)
      [On microfilm. Master negative number 2000-2030. See also In Masks Outrageous and Austere]
    - The Glass Menagerie, [v.p.], 1945-1947, (Typed script, programs, clippings, poster [acq Friends 55052E] Screenplay [acq 255016], Pressbook [acq No. 278104]) (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
    - The Glass Menagerie, [n.p.], 1945-1982, (Programs, clippings, reviews, articles, French version by Marcel Duhamel) (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - [The Gnadiges Fraulein], [n.p.], ca. 1966, (12 pp. t.ms., letter [acq 487/490-7/1/88]) (Box 9, Folder 8)
      [See also Slapstick Tragedy]
    - The Gnadiges Fraulein, [n.p.], 1970, (Script pages, clippings) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - A House Not Meant To Stand, [n.p.], [n.d.], (Annotated script pages) (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - A House Not Meant to Stand, [n.p.], April, 1981, (2 Scripts, Post Goodman Studio version, April 1981, photocopied) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - A House Not Meant To Stand, [n.p.], 1981-1982, (2 scripts, post Goodman Studio version, April 1981; 2 scripts, revised February, 1982, mimeographed [Lyle Leverich copy acq 3-8-1990, 297]) (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
    - A House Not Made To Stand, [n.p.], 1981-1982, (Clippings, programs, flyers) (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - I Never Get Dressed till After Dark on Sundays, [n.p.], [n.d.], (25 p. mimeograph typescript) (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - In Masks Outrageous and Austere, [n.p.], 1979-1980, (Mimeographed script, second draft, August 1979 to June 1980) (Box 10, Folder 7)
      [On microfilm. Master negative number 2000-2030
      See also Gideon's Point and Tent Worms]
    - In the Bar of a Tokyo Hotel, [n.p.], 1969-1970, (Draft pages, mimeographed annotated script, March 22, 1969, 1970 program [acq. 401562C]) (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - In the Bar of a Tokyo Hotel, [n.p.], 1972, (Clippings) (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Intruder, [n.p.], [n.d.], (Annotated t. ms.) (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Kind of Love, [n.p.], [n.d.], (34 pp. annotated t.ms. [acq 487/490-7.1.88]) (Box 10, Folder 11)
      Also known as A Small Object for a Cobra and Minerva's Head]
    - Kingdom of Earth, New York, June 1967, (117 p. t.ms.s., mimeographed [acq 255 014]) (Box 10, Folder 12)
      [See also short story and Seven Descents of Myrtle]
    - Kingdom of Earth, [n.p.], 1967-1973, (Mimeographed script revised June 1967, clippings) (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kirche, Kutchen, und Kinder, [n.p.], [n.d.], (Annotated script) (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Lady's Choice, [n.p.], 1982, (3 mimeographed screenplays, script pages) (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
      [Screen adaptation of Williams short stories written with Peter Hoffman]
    - Lady's Choice, [n.p.], September 22, 1982, (Mimeographed screenplay) (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Lady's Choice, [n.p.], October 4, 1982, (Mimeographed screenplay) (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Lady's Choice, [n.p.], November 22, 1982, (Mimeographed screenplay) (Box 11, Folder 7)
      [On microfilm. Master negative number 2000-2031
      Screen adaptation of Williams short stories written with Peter Hoffman]
    - Last of my Solid Gold Watches, [n.p.], [n.d.], (27 p. mimeographed t.ms. [acq 255017]) (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Life Boat Drill, New York, [n.d.], (Mimeographed script) (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Lovely Sunday for Creve Coeur, [n.p.], 1979-1982, (Mimeographed 1978 script [Lyle Leverich copy]; Clippings, book jacket) (Box 12, Folder 1)
      [See also Creve Coeur]
    - The Milk Train Doesn't Stop Here Anymore, [n.p.], [n.d.], (a.ms. draft pages [acq 07918C]) (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
      [See also Boom]
    - The Milk Train Doesn't Stop Here Anymore, [n.p.], [1963], (2 annotated scripts, No. 1, 2, and duplicate pages [acq 07918C]) (Box 12, Folder 4-6)